<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

<LitF.Update.Title>LittleFairy UpdateInfo</LitF.Update.Title>

<LitF.Update.label>
2023/05/20(0.3.0.0):
*B.E.P Race Core is required as a prerequisite mod, and common parts have been greatly reduced.
If you are using an earlier version, various data such as hairstyles and clothes have been lost.
If you need an older version, you can download the mod before the update by going to github from the mod page.

2023/04/08(0.2.4.1):
*Fixed a problem that prevented the possession of LittleFairy ideology from performing jobs that would open up in slavery status.

*Added clarification that Little Fairy's skills cannot be used while down.

2023/03/27(0.2.4.0):
*Fixed some bugs

*Fixed some graphics

*Separated FacialAnimation definitions into separate mods
To reduce the load at startup, I have separated FacialAnimation images and definitions into separate mods.
Please subscribe from the collection.

2023/03/05(0.2.3.0):
*LittleFairies now appear dressed according to their roles

*Some bugs have been fixed

2023/01/31(0.2.2.5):
*Removed race restrictions on research

*Armor values of some equipment have been adjusted

2023/01/30(0.2.2.4):
*Various statuses are no longer corrected based on age

2023/01/29(0.2.2.3):
*Increased the number of hairstyle types to 8

2023/01/28(0.2.2.2):
*Fixed a bug that nursery data could not be saved correctly when trying to save after using a nursery
Please dismantle the nursery once, as this change could cause information to be corrupted

*Allowed settlers and slaves other than Little Fairy to enter the nursery on their own

*Brainwashing collars are now available for Sweety

2023/01/16(0.2.2.1):
*The market value of bloody armor has been significantly reduced, and the armor values of slashing and striking have been significantly reduced

2023/01/15(0.2.2.0):
*Architect categories have been merged

*The amount of damage received by the Little Fairies of the hostile faction can now be adjusted in the config

*New clothes added

2023/01/08(0.2.1.5):
*The setting was changed so that the gene of Biotech's appearance system cannot be adapted

2023/01/06(0.2.1.4):
*Support for the function of fertility change through Biotech linkage of HAR

*Fixed a bug that prevented inherited buffs from being loaded when loading save data

2022/12/12(0.2.1.3):
*Some small fixes were made

2022/12/08(0.2.1.1):
*Brainwashing collars can now be used against Glassy

2022/12/07(0.2.1.0):
*When FP is 0, the skill button cannot be pressed

*Some small fixes were made

2022/11/23(0.2.0.8):
*Skin and hair colors are no longer changed by genes

*Adjusted behavior of source code

2022/11/12(0.2.0.6):
*Brainwashing collars can now be used even when the target is not a player faction.
However, if the target belongs to a faction, the faction will become hostile the moment it is used, except under certain circumstances.

*Mods are now interlocked with each other.

*Mofy the whitefox in a cold land race*
Mofy can now be brainwashed with a brainwashing collar.
However, the faction will turn against you.

*Resurreviewy the nxious about immortality race*
Resurreviewy the nxious about immortality race
However, if there are other Resurreviewy around, they will run amok and become hostile

2022/11/06(0.2.0.5):
*Body shape graphics and costume graphics have been re-created

*Resolved the problem of misaligned drawing of children's heads

*Facial Animation elements have been adjusted.
Some data has been adjusted by re-creating graphics.
Some parts have been deleted. Please use mods such as CharacterEditer to correct them.

2022/10/30(0.2.0.4):
*The specification that made the face unique has been eliminated.
For existing saved data, please use CharacterEditer or other mods to correct this issue.

*Fixed a problem in which wild little faeries that appeared sometimes learned one skill category in duplicate.

*When creating a little faerie whose parent has already been created, the parent's abilities are now inherited and spawned.

2022/10/12(0.2.0.2):
*Fixed a bug that caused the display of nursery progress to remain at 0%.

2022/10/11(0.2.0.1):
*Slaves and prisoners can now be offered even if they are not down.

2022/10/10(0.2.0.0):
*Fixed some bugs.

*Compatible with 1.4 (Wip)
1: Added body shape in child state, etc.
Some equipment, such as armor, cannot be equipped in the child state.
Also, the movement speed is a little slower than that of adults.

*The price of meat has been slightly increased.

*The gestation period has been shortened from 10 to 6 days.

*Added some configurations
1: It is now possible to give birth as an adult.
Without BioTech DLC, some features are not available, so they are turned on by default.
If you have BioTech, it is recommended to turn it off.

*Special abilities are no longer available for children.

2022/10/07(0.1.0.2):
*Added a hairstyle.

*Decreased the performance of the MeatCleaver.

*Added a new outfit.

*added 3 new collars, collars can be created with new research.

*added a new totem.

*added new configurations.

*some bugs fixed.

2022/10/04(0.1.0.1):
*Translation flaws have been corrected.

*Hairstyle added.

*[NL] Facial Animation - WIP is now supported.

*Configuration has been added.

*New "Succession" common skill has been added.
"Succession" will be applied to the AlienRace in use and may produce little faeries with a passive skill that buffs the abilities of their race when placed in the nursery.
The amount of effect of the buff depends on how far away from the human the race is.
If you want to know the details of the buffs, you can find them in the status menu of the nursery where the tribe was submitted.
The amount of the buff's effect can be adjusted in the configuration.
</LitF.Update.label>

</LanguageData>